

# Mateusz Lota



Poland, Łódź



mateuszlota112@gmail.com



+48 510 817 777

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/mateusz-lota

GitHub: github.com/MateuszLota

### **SUMMARY:**

I have a great desire and motivation to start a new role in Testing industry. Thanks to technical education and past experience, I have the skills of being meticulous and inquisitive. Creating diffrent types of tests are not a problem.

I am good at multi-tasking as well as when it comes to time management skills.

I'm fond of New technologies and mountain biking, I take part in amateur competitions, reaching my goals despite any difficulties. I like learning new things and developing my skills, both personal and professional.

#### MAIN SKILLS:

- · Basic of: HTML, CSS, SQL
- · Basic of: Java, JS
- ISTQB knowledge
- Basic of: Jmeter
- · Basic of: Postman, API
- Otest, TestLink, Jira
- · Creating test cases and test scenarios
- Making test plans
- · Agile, SCRUM, Canban
- Spanish A2
- English B2/C1

# **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

#### WORK&TRAVEL USA

May 2022 - Oct 2022

- Working with international clients.
- Creating plans and giving reports from it.
- Helping with configurations of computer systems
- Solving urgent problems.

#### IT SUPPORT

KONCEPT SYSTEMY INFORMATYCZNE S.C. | Oct 2022 – Apr 2022

- Remote users support.
- Installation and configuration of operating systems.
- Configuration of routers and servers.
- printer repair and configuration

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE

DECATHLON | Sept 2021 - Nov 2022

- · Assembling and repairing bikes.
- Customer service and advice.
- Planning the distribution of goods
- Solving urgent problems

#### HELP DESK

SEBDAN | Sept 2020 - Dec 2020

- Installation and configuration of operating systems.
- · Configuration of routers and servers.
- Assembling computers

## **EDUCATION:**

## University of Lodz

Oct 2023

studies major: Computer Sience

Coders Lab | Manual Tester Bootcamp Mar - Jun 2023

GEODETIC AND TECHNICAL SCHOOLS IN IT technician LODZ:

Vocational secondary school | 2017 - 2021

# **CERTYFICATES**

- ISTQB FL Certyficate
- UDEMY | Fundamentals of manual software testing Course Credential URL: Certificate Link
- CAMBRIDGE Assessment | FIRST
- EE08 Certificate (Installation and operation of computer systems, peripherals and networks)
- EE09 Certificate (Programming, development and administration of websites and databases)

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation). I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purposes necessary for the recruitment process (in accordance with the Personal Data Protection
Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and in accordance with Regulation (EU)
2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (RODO).